Hi, this is Yolanda Vanveen from vanveenbulbs.com.
In this segment we'll talk about, what kind of flowers should I put in my yard?
Now when I garden, I always remember that it's my garden, and your garden is your garden, and it's all about you.
So when I'm planting flowers in my garden, I try not to take too many things too seriously, because in the end it's all about me and what I enjoy.
And so, I like to look on the Internet, onto different websites that give you lots of different ideas on what to plant in your garden, but when it comes down to it, I just collect plants wherever I go, and that's a good rule of thumb.
If you go to a garden center, farmers market, and you see something that you like, and you've got a sunny spot, and it will do well in the sun, plant it there.
You don't always have to know the names of everybody that comes to your party to enjoy their company, so I try to remember the names of the plants that I purchase, but of course I forget some of the names, and in the end, that doesn't really matter, because all that matter is, that you enjoy your garden, because it is an extension of you.
You can have a very formal garden with everything marked, and everything simple, and not very crowded, or you can have just a big summer party and a big barbecue bash, and you can mix and match all different types of plants that like the sun or the shade, and just put groups of them all over, and you can move them around later, and you don't have to be strict with it either, it's whatever you want to do.
So my favorite plants that I have in my garden, and that I would definitely recommend, are the following plants; this is my gold, millennium gold calla-lily, it likes full hot sun, and I love it because its got spotted leaves, and its got these bright lemony yellow flowers that last almost all summer long, and it will keep blooming for lots and lots of periods of time, and I love that it'll do full hot sun, more than shade, because I've got a lot of sun and it does really well.
This Cleopatra canna-lily is of course one of my most favorite plants in my garden, and I've got some in the garden, I've got some in containers, I love the striped leaves.
So when you're picking out plants, make sure to take in account what the leaves look like, what the fragrances are, and if they're not fragrant, if they are fragrant, and it's all about you again.
I love the spots, and I love the different textures of the Cleopatra, it's gorgeous.
And I love all the tropical plants that we can get away with growing in the northwest.
This is my mandevilla, or my mande-villa plants, and it's just a vine, but I love the bright red flowers, and I love that humming birds really, really enjoy it.
And next to that I have my gladiolus meriali, are also know as acidenthera, and I just love it, it has a nice fragrance like grape bubblegum, and it has little spots in the middle that are burgundy, that are just gorgeous, so it's a really, really, really pretty plant.
But there's another ten thousand to a hundred thousand plants that we haven't talked about.
So gardening to me is just like meeting everybody else that you meet in your life, you enjoy their company when they're there, and you invite them over whenever you can, but you realized that you can't possibly have every plant in the world in your garden, and it's about change, some plants stay for years and years, some plants go away after two years, but I never take it personally, because I know there's many more plants that I can meet in the future, that will enjoy my garden.
So when I'm trying to decide what kind of plants to put in my garden, I look through magazines, I look through web pages, I look through different websites that have different ideas, and I realize that plants will never do the same in my yard as they do in other peoples yards, just as people will never act the same at your parties as they will at other peoples parties, but in the end, it really doesn't matter, all that matters is that you have a good time at your garden, and that's my advice, just plant plants when you can find them, and enjoy their company when you can.